Guide to the Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics records, 1953-2010.
Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics records, 1950-2009.
14-22-3898
Cornell University.Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics (LEPP).
31 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications written by Cornell physicists and colliding beam experiment reports.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications written by Cornell physicists and colliding beam experiment reports.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University.Dept. of Physics; Wilson Synchrotron Laboratory (Cornell University)
Subjects:
Nuclear physics--Research.; Particle accelerators-Construction.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also collection #14-22-3483, Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics Photographs
See also https://www.classe.cornell.edu/public/README.html, LEPP Web Site
See also https://www.classe.cornell.edu/Research/CESR/WebHome.html, CESR Homepage
See also https://www.classe.cornell.edu/Research/CLEO/, CLEO Homepage
SERIES LIST
Series I. Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX)
Boxes 1-8
Series II: Colliding Beam Notes (CBN)
Boxes 19-21
Series III: Cornell Lab of Nuclear Studies Notes (CLNS)
Boxes 8-19, 22-24
Series IV: CSN
Boxes 21,22
Series V: Cornell Electron Storage Ring (CESR/CLEO) Proposals, Reports, Presentations
Boxes 10, 22, 24, 25, 27-31
Series VI: Energy Recovery Linac (ERL)
Boxes 25, 27
Series VII: National Science Foundation (NSF)
Boxes 26, 27, 29
Series VIII: Other Proposals, Reports, Manuals, Memos, and Articles
Boxes 24, 25, 27, 29, 31
Series IX: Conferences, Workshops
Boxes 10, 22-25, 27, 29, 31
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1975-1984 (Box 1)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1984-1991 (Box 2)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1991-1994 (Box 3)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1994-1996 (Box 4)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 2000-2001 (Box 7)
  - Colliding Beam Experiment Reports (CBX), 2001-2003 (Box 8)
- Series II. Colliding Beam Notes (CBN)
  - CBN, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - CBN, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - CBN, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - CBN, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - CBN, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - CBN, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - CBN, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - CBN, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - CBN, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - CBN, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - CBN, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - CBN, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - CBN, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - CBN, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - CBN, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - CBN, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - CBN, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - CBN, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - CBN, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - CBN, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - CBN, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - CBN, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - CBN, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - CBN, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - CBN, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - CBN, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - CBN, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - CBN, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - CBN, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - CBN, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - CBN, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - CBN, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - CBN, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - CBN, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - CBN, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - CBN, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - CBN, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - CBN, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - CBN, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - CBN, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - CBN, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - CBN, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - CBN, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - CBN, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - CBN, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - CBN, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Series III: Cornell Lab of Nuclear Studies Notes (CLNS)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes -#37-57, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes -#58-63, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #64-71, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #72-75, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #76-78, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #79-84, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #85-89, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #90-97, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #98-104, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #105-112, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #113-117, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #118-124, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #125-132, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #133-137, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #138-145, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #146-152, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #153-157, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #158-163, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #164-168, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #169-179, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #173-183, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #184-189, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #190-195, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #196-200, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #201-202, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #203-211, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #212-217, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #218-224, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #225-230, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #231-236, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #237-242, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #243-247, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #248-254, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #255-260, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #261-268, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #269-275, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #276-288, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #288-293, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #294-296, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #297-305, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #306-308, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #309-310, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #311-319, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #320, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #316-321, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #322-328, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #329-332, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #333, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #334-336, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #337-339, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #340-342, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #343, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #344-349, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #350-358, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #359-363, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #364-374, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #375-378, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #379-382, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #383-387, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #388-396, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #397-406, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #407-415, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #416-417, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #418-424, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #425, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #426-430, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #431-438, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #439-447, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #448-455, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #457-467, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #468-470, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #471-476, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #477-479, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #480-489, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #492-496, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #497-504, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #505, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #506-509, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #510-513, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #514-518, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #519-522, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #523-528, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #529-539, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #540-548, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #549-560, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #561-567, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #568-578, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #579-589, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #590-599, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #600-609, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #610-618, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #619-628, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #629-631, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #632-633, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #634, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #635-644, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #645-654, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #655-664, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #665-710, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #711-731, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #732-750, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #751-762, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #52-69, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #70-74, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #75-88, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #89-103, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #104-118, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #830-836, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #837-852, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #853-858, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #861-866, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #867-877, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #878-892, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #893-912, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #913-931, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #932-941, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #942-951, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #952-960, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #961-962, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #963-967, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #968-974, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #975-983, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #984-988, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #989-1002, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1003-1010, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1011-1014, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1015-1021, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1022-1028, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1029 Pt.1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1029 Pt.2, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1030-1034, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1035-1040, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1042-1046, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1047-1049, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1050 Pt.1, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1050 Pt.2, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1052-1055, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1056-1057, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1058-1059, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1060-1069, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1070-1085, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1086-1096, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1097-1101, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1102-1106, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1107-1114, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1115-1119, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1120-1121, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1122, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1123-1127, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1128-1132, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1133-1134, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1136-1141, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1142-1147, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1148-1152, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1153-1156, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1157-1162, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1163-1170, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1171-1176, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1177-1184, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1185-1191, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1192-1198, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1200-1211, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1212-1229, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1230-1237, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1238-1243, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1244-1250, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1251-1259, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1260-1265, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1266-1274, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1275-1279, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1280-1292, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1293-1303, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1304-1316, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1317-1327, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1328-1337, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1338-1350, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1351-1360, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1361-1369, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1370-1380, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1381-1387, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1389-1396, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1397-1403, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1404-1409, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1410-1414, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1415-1430, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1431-1441, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1442-1452, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1453-1459, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1460-1467, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1468-1480, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1481-1486, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1487, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1488-1499, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1500-1509, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1510-1520, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1521-1528, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1529-1538, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1539-1544, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1545-1550, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1551-1561, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1562-1573, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1574-1583, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1584-1600, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1601-1607, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1608-1612, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1612, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1613-1626, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1627-1656, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1660-1664, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1665-1673, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1674-1680, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #16681-1690, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)